### Contact

415-758-8883 fedortnn@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/fedortsyganov (LinkedIn) fedor-tsyganov.github.io (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

- Leadership
- Organization of testing process

### Languages

- English
- Russian

### Certifications

Java Programming Android App Programming (App Development)

iPhone App Programming (iOS App Development)

# Fedor Tsyganov

Software Quality Engineer at Adobe

San Francisco, California

# Summary

Software QA Engineer who focuses on writing clean, elegant and efficient test automation code and have a passion for designing beautiful and functional user experiences. I'm a dedicated and quality-focused engineer with hands-on experience in mobile, web, and cloud. I have outstanding interpersonal and communication skills, and I demonstrate superior accuracy in writing and maintaining technical documentation.

# Experience

#### Adobe

Software Quality Engineer December 2017 - Present San Francisco Bay Area

Quality Engineer II September 2017 - December 2017

San Francisco Bay Area

Y Media Labs Software Quality Assurance Engineer April 2017 - August 2017 Redwood City, CA

#### Clickatell

Software Quality Assurance Engineer September 2016 - April 2017 Redwood City, CA

#### **QAUBER**

Software Automation QA Engineer January 2015 - August 2016

Santa Clara, CA

Open California Content Manager August 2011 - May 2012

Gathering and creating content, real estate market research, working with informational database for the startup company by using internet technologies.

Snikers Urbania youth initiative Community Organizer August 2007 - August 2008 Nizhny Novgorod Region Area, Russian Federation

Organized a community initiative to participate in Snikers Urbania contest program for building a skatepark in one of partipating Russian region. The rules of the contest were geting as many votes as possible both online, on the Snikers Urbania website, and offline, on Snikers Urbania event. By a hard work and collaboration with local youth active leaders we won the contest with about 30.000 unique online votes and about 20.000 unique offline votes. The grand prise of the contest was building a skate park by Snikers (\$15.000-20.000). It was the first professional and public skate park in the region.

Competition was held among major Russian regions such as Moscow, Saint Petersburg, and etc.

(In population, Nizhny Novgorod region 10 times smaller than Moscow and 5 times smaller than Saint Petersburg)

## Education

City College of San Francisco Computer Science (2013 - 2016)

State University — Higher School of Economics
Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management,
General · (2009 - 2013)